<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href = "destinations.xsl" type = "text/xsl" ?>
<destinations> <!-- xmlns="http://www.w3schools.com" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"-->
  <country id="c1">
    <name>United Kingdom</name>
    <descriptions>A political union of Britain, Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland, the UK has an astounding mix of societies to offer. It's no more drawn out the universe of top caps and strolling sticks; rather you'll discover a land saturated with heavenly history, and home to a vivacious music scene and beguiling field. London is the place to go for both music and a great deal of those scandalous locales. Stroll around the Places of Parliament and Huge Ben, Up in Scotland, the magnificence of Edinburgh and famous grit of Glasgow are both enormous draws. Make a beeline for the good countries to discover natural manors, ancient estates.Northern Ireland is a flight (or boat ride) away, however justified regardless of the bother for the magnificence of Belfast.h</descriptions>
    <ratings>4</ratings>
    <post>
      <comments>
        
      </comments>
    </post>
 </country>
  
   <country id="c2">
    <name>Italy</name>
    <descriptions>In capital Rome you'll discover copious hints of the Roman Domain in the Colosseum and the innumerable disintegrating landmarks spread all through the city. Vatican City, a little nation inside the city's limits, rouses guests with the specialty of the Sistine House of prayer, the love of St Subsides and the historical backdrop of the Vatican Exhibition halls, and additionally the harlequin hues and staunch mien of the renowned Swiss Watch. At that point there's the Trevi Wellspring, the Spanish Strides, the Supreme Gatherings, Piazza Navona&#x2026;

Sentimental people will discover riding the rising waters of Venice and investigating its renaissance design an overwhelming draw, venturing out of their inn specifically onto a bending longboat. In as much as they stay away from the undeniably regular floods, that is. Florence, and its unlimited columns of red-roofed houses aren't a long ways behind.</descriptions>
    <ratings>3</ratings>
    <post>
      <comments>
        
      </comments>
    </post>
  </country>
  
  <country id="c3">
    <name>Spain</name>
    <descriptions>As a famously showy corner of what Europeans joyfully consider as 'sunbathing domain', Spain is home to an inviting blend of Mediterranean culture and its own particular interesting (and frequently conflicting) standards). As the enthusiastic country home to flamenco and bull battling in a few corners, and in addition awesome fish and strong alcoholic espresso, this is a nation that is just as tempting off the beaten track as on, so much so that an Englishman as of late invested months sitting by a telephone confine a 'social examination'. We can't help supposing it was more for no particular reason... Investigate cosmopolitan Barcelona, lounge on the shorelines of Andaluc&#xED;a and climb among the rough pinnacles of the Pyrenees. Retaining the way of life is a basic part of a Spanish trek; you'll need to get used to lunchtime rests, olives with each feast.</descriptions>
    <ratings>5</ratings>
    <post>
      <comments>
        
      </comments>
    </post>
  </country>
  
  <country id="c4">
    <name>France</name>
    <descriptions>From the notorious structures and tasteful cooking styles of Paris to the vineyards of Champagne, most voyagers are more than mindful of France's amazing (and sentimental) resume, and as of now have the nation of culture high on their voyaging hit list.

Paris doesn't disillusion for sure, with the greatness of the Seine (and it's scandalously partitioned east and west banks), the class of Notre Lady and the sentiment of nightfall over the Eiffel Tower. Best of all, it's not only the locales that are captivating.</descriptions>
    <ratings>3</ratings>
    <post>
      <comments>
        
      </comments>
    </post>
  </country>
  
  <country id="c5">
    <name>Germany</name>
    <descriptions>A place that is known for dynamic urban communities and sensitive, manor covered wide open, Germany blends the old and the new into a tantalizing touristic mix. From the Lederhosen and plentiful, maturing brew lobbies to the world capital of techno and streets without speed limits, there are few who won't discover something to love.

In case you're a city sort, Berlin's reality class galleries, insuppressible techno parties (in case you're a substantial move aficionado, Berlin's decadent yearly 'Love Parade' is most likely your concept of paradise) and look at the narrowing city partition and what's left of the Berlin Divider. Munich has it's own motivation, gladly saturated with Bavarian culture and overflowing with conventional lederhosen-filled lager corridors. Once per year, Oktoberfest comes to town, and appears to carry a large portion of the world with it. Welcome to another relentless, lager swilling German gathering.</descriptions>
    <ratings>4</ratings>
    <post>
      <comments>
        
      </comments>
    </post>
  </country>
  
  <country id="c6">
    <name>Netherlands</name>
    <descriptions>The Netherlands is the place where there is windmills, whores and lawful medications. In any event that is the thing that you presumably definitely think about the nation, yet those are only the feature producers: what for the most part shocks is that this little corner of Europe is overwhelmingly lovely. Yes, capital Amsterdam is an indulgent play area where you can do things you wouldn't dream of doing at home, and yes it has its own particular sex exhibition hall. Among the lanes of Europe's most tolerant city, be that as it may, are tranquil, winding trenches, cobbled paths, patio nurseries of clear tulips and a glorious building brimming with the works of Van Gogh. So no, it's not only for gathering creatures and stag evenings, however most guests wind up in a caf&#xE9;, or floating through the shady area of town at some stage (only for diversion estimation obviously &#x2013; don't have a go at taking photos!).</descriptions>
    <ratings>5</ratings>
    <post>
      <comments>
        
      </comments>
    </post>
  </country>
  
  <country id="c7">
    <name>Ireland</name>
    <descriptions>Ireland - home of numerous well known essayists, artists, vocalists and music, of St Patrick, Guinness, bourbon and a unimaginably huge number of outstanding bars &#x2013; can be stormy, now and again even devastate, yet never not exactly uncommonly fun. Ireland has profited significantly from its EU enrollment, and nearby all the old conventions &#x2013; the late night bar singalongs and little however perfectly picturesque cultivating groups &#x2013; you'll discover the island of Ireland is moving with the circumstances.</descriptions>
    <ratings>4</ratings>
   <post>
      <comments>
        
      </comments>
    </post>
  </country>
  
  <country id="c8">
    <name>Belgium</name>
    <descriptions>One of the establishing individuals from the European Union, Belgium has for quite some time been viewed as one of the junction of Europe, where the Germanic and Latin societies meet. The nation is known globally for its solid lagers, its waffles and chocolates, its landscape, and its casual perspectives on governmental issues, religion, sexuality, and life by and large.

The Romans gave Belgium its name when they made the area of Gallia Belgica in the principal century BC. Throughout the years the nation has seen a changing line of rulers from a few distinct nations until the establishing of the nation in 1830. From that point forward the nation has been a sacred government and parliamentary majority rules system and a herald in European mix through the Benelux and the EU, has made ready for other European nations to follow afterward.</descriptions>
    <ratings>3</ratings>
   <post>
      <comments>
        
      </comments>
    </post>
  </country>
  
  <country id="c9">
    <name>Turkey</name>
    <descriptions>A standout amongst the most essential nations as far as area as an extension amongst Europe and Asia, and a standout amongst the most socially critical nations with a history going back to ancient circumstances, Turkey straddles the crevice amongst Asia and Europe along the Dark Ocean, the Mediterranean Ocean, and the Aegean Ocean, while in the meantime offering outskirts to Bulgaria, Greece, Armenia, Azerbaijan, Georgia, Syria, Iraq, and Iran. The nation as it exists today was initially framed in 1923. It is a boundless cluster of various geology, and the atmosphere ranges from run of the mill beach front territories along the coastlines of the Mediterranean, Aegean, and the Dark Oceans, while the outskirt along the south close Syria is abandon, and parts of the inside are forested and precipitous.</descriptions>
    <ratings>3</ratings>
   <post>
      <comments>
        
      </comments>
    </post>
  </country>
  
  <country id="c10">
    <name>Poland</name>
    <descriptions>One of the Baltic countries in Focal Europe flanked by Belarus, the Czech Republic, Germany, Lithuania, Russia, Slovakia, and the Ukraine, Poland figures out how to emerge among the rest with its rich history, astonishing farmland, and its unmistakable social interest. From its first settlement in Biskupin at some point before the seventh century BC, to its Roman roots, and the possible brilliant time amid the fourteenth through the sixteenth century when its kingdom extended from the Baltic to the Dark and Adriatic oceans, Poland has for some time been a standard of strength inside the locale. But then, for a nation with such a respectable legacy, Poland has been invade a larger number of times than most, because of its key area in Europe. It has seen more than its share of war, yet the nation has bounced back over and over as of recently it stands, pleased and straight, as it walks into the 21st century.</descriptions>
    <ratings>2</ratings>
    <post>
      <comments>
        
      </comments>
    </post>
  </country>


</destinations>
